videoleapapp.com 2019-03-03

# PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT

                                              LIGHTRICKS - PRIVACY NOTICE
Lightricks Ltd. ("​Lightricks​", “​we​”, “​us​”, “​our​”) provides users with apps designed to edit and perfect photos,
create images and share your creations through social media and email (the "​Apps​"). Our Apps include
Facetune, Facetune 2, Enlight, Enlight Photofox, Enlight Videoleap, Enlight Quickshot and more. This Privacy
Notice (the "​Notice​") describes the how we collect and use your personal data through our Apps. It also
describes the rights and options available to you with respect to your personal information.
                                                       WHO WE ARE
                                    Lightricks Ltd. is the data controller of the personal data we collect via the
   We       are     the     data
             controller of the      Apps and use and share as further described below.
             personal       data
             we collect via         We are located at Professor Racah St, Building 5.4, Jerusalem, Israel, 91904.
             the Apps.
                                                        CONTACT US
                                    If you have any questions or requests concerning your personal data or
   How to contact our Data
             Protection             about our privacy practices and policies, you may contact our Data
             Officer                Protection Officer at: ​dpo@lightricks.com
                                    The European representative of Lightricks, for purposes of this Notice will be
   How      to contact our
             European               Lightricks UK Inc., If you are within the European Economic Area, you may
             representative         contact our European representative the at the following address:
                                    eu.representative@lightricks.com
                                          PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT
                                    When you use our Apps, we will record and collect the following
   We      collect analytical
             information            information (collectively, "​Analytical Information​"):
             about your use
             of the Apps.                  1.    Unique operational identifiers​, that allow us to identify a user
                                                 across multiple devices.
                                           2.    Unique advertising identifiers​, We use it for advertising as we
                                                 further describe in this Notice.
                                           3.    IP address from which you access the Apps. We can also identify
                                                 your geo-location via your IP address.
                                           4.    Device information​, including device type, operating system
                                                 version, time zone and your preferred languages.
                                           5.    Usage information​, such as the time and date you accessed the
                                                 Apps, the features you used, your preferences and for how long
                                                 you use an App every time you launch it.
   If you made an in-app            If you choose to subscribe to our VIP/PRO accounts or to purchase items
             purchase – we          through our Apps, we will collect the information provided by Apple on the
             will receive your      respective invoice ("​Purchase Information​").
             receipt       from
             Apple

The overall personal data outlined above will be referred to as the "​Information​".
                                          SOURCE OF PERSONAL DATA
We do not collect the Information we disclosed above only by ourselves. We obtain some of it from the
following sources ("​Vendors​"):
     1.   AppsFlyer​, Inc. AppsFlyer's privacy policy is available ​here​.
          you can opt-out of AppsFlyer Analytics tracking by sending an email to: ​privacy@appsflyer.com​;
     2.   Taplytics, Inc.​; Taplytics' privacy policy is available ​here​.
     3.   Firebase​ (Google); Taplytics' privacy policy is available ​here​.
     4.   Facebook​; Facebook's privacy policy is available ​here​.
The Vendors may also collect your Information through their designated code incorporated in our Apps. We
use their services for the purposes set forth below.
                                         HOW WE USE PERSONAL DATA
    We use your Information          We use your Information for the following purposes:
              to improve and
              enhance         the         1.  Maintain and improve our Apps;
              Apps and our                2.  Develop new services and features​;
              services.
                                          3.  Enrich the content and features available on our Apps;
                                          4.  Adapt the Apps, its features and functionality to users' preferences​;
                                          5.  Analysis of marketing efficiency​.
The legal basis under EU law for processing and collecting Analytical Data is our legitimate interests in
operating our Apps, ongoing management of our business and business development.
    We      also use your            Subject to your informed consent, in some of our products (Facetune on the
              Information to         Google Play Store) we will use the Analytical Information we obtain to serve
              provide you with
              personalized           you with advertisements to products and services that we believe may suit
              services               your interests.
The legal basis under EU law for collecting and processing your Information for profiled advertising purposes
is your explicit consent.
                   WHEN AND HOW WE SHARE PERSONAL DATA WITH OTHERS
We will not share your information with third-parties, except in the events listed below or when you provide
us your explicit and informed consent
                                     We will share your Information with our service providers who assist us to
    We         share         your
              Information with operate our Apps. Our service providers are authorized to use your
              the        service Information only as necessary to provide us with their services and not for
              providers who
                                     their own purposes. We do not sell your Information to third parties.
              assist    us     in
              operating       our
              business and the
              Apps
                                     If you have breached the terms of use of the Apps, this Notice or any other
    We     will share your
              Information            agreement you have with Lightricks, abused your rights to use the Apps, or

       when          you   violated any applicable law - Your Information will be shared with third
       violate the terms   parties (such as legal counsels and advisors), who handle the matter on our
       of           your
       engagement          behalf, or with the competent authorities.
       with Lightricks
                           If we are bound to disclose your information by a judicial order or by a
We   will share your
       Information      if governmental or regulatory authority acting within its legal authority, we
       we are legally      will comply and share the Information.
       required.
                           If we organize the operation of our company within a different framework,
We   will share your
       Information      if or through another legal structure or entity (such as due to a merger or
       we         change   acquisition) - we will share your Information to enable the structural
       Lightrick's
                           change. However, the receiving party will be bound by this Notice.
       business
       structure.
                              SECURITY AND DATA RETENTION
                           We retain personal data as long as we need it for the purposes for which it
How long will we retain
       your                was obtained or until you ask to delete it. If you ask us to delete the
       Information.        Information, we may still have to retain it to comply with our legal
                           obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
                           We implement measures to reduce the risks of damage, loss of information
We implement measures
       to secure your      and unauthorized access or use of information. However, these measures
       Information         do not provide absolute information security. Therefore, although efforts
                           are made to secure your personal information, it is not guaranteed, and you
                           cannot expect that the Service will be immune from information security
                           risks.
                            INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS
                           We are based in the State of Israel. The Information we collect from you will
We will transfer your
       Information to      be processed in Israel, which is recognized by the European Union ("EU") ​as
       third countries     having adequate protection for personal data.
       only            in
       accordance with     We will only transfer your Information from within the EU to other
       applicable data     jurisdictions if they have been deemed to have an adequate level of data
       protection laws.
                           protection by the EU, or as otherwise permitted by the applicable data
                           protection laws.
                                        YOUR EU RIGHTS
                           If you are in the EU, you have the right to access the personal information
You have the right to
       access, update      about you that we store on our systems, and have us update, correct or
       or delete your      delete it. You are also entitled to obtain from us your Information (excluding
       Information and
                           data we obtained from other sources) in a structured, commonly used and
       obtain a copy of
       your                machine-readable format, and have the right to transmit those data to
       Information.        another data controller. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, contact

                             us at ​contact@lightricks.com​.
                             If you are in the EU, you can lodge a complaint to the supervisory authority
   You have a right to
           submit          a under the General data Protection Regulations ("GDPR"), in particular in the
           complaint to the  Member State of your residence, place of work or where the alleged
           relevant
                             infringement of the GDPR occured. For a list of supervisory authorities in the
           supervisory data
           protection        EU, click ​here​.
           authority.
                                               MINORS
                             The Apps are not intended for minors under the age of 13. IF YOU ARE
   You must be at least 13
           years of age to   UNDER THE AGE OF 13 YOU MAY NOT USE THE APPS.
           use the Apps.
                              CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE
                             From time to time, we may change this Notice. If you are a registered user,
   If we change this Notice,
           we will notify    we will provide you notice of such changes through the Apps. In case of legal
           you in advance.   requirement, we may also introduce immediate changes to the Notice and
                             require that you accept them. In any event, if you do not consent to the
                             amended Notice, we may terminate your user account. The latest version of
                             the Notice will always be accessible on the Apps.
Last Update​: May 24, 2018
